Hello.
안녕하세요
Nice to meet you. You must be Kasane.
처음 뵙겠습니다 카사네 씨 맞죠
From now on, we'll be sisters.
오늘부터 우리가 자매 될 거예요
I'm your elder sister, and you're my little sister.
저는 언니고 카사네는 동생이에요
I hope we get along, Kasane.
잘 부탁드립니다 카사네 씨
Sister...
언... 니...
SCARLET NEXUS
《스칼렛넥서》
♪A crime in reality♪
현실한 Crime
♪For Heaven's sake♪
For Heaven's sake
♪Accepts any fake♪
거짓을 받아들여
♪And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♪
영원한 환상 점차 사라지고
♪Won't take it at all, I get sick♪
완벽 절대 아님 I get sick
♪A girl looking back♪
몸을 돌려 걸어온 소녀
♪Casts the miracle into the instant world♪
이 순간의 세상에 기적이 내려와
♪Did you lie♪
Did you lie
♪Spit the venom♪
Spit the venom
♪I know why♪
I know why
♪I've found a game of ecstasy♪
찾았다 기막힌 게임
♪Red Criminal gets life♪
Red Criminal gets life
♪I've never been in love♪
I've never been in love
♪Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♪
언제부터 이런 세상이 지겨워졌는지
♪We will fly♪
We will fly
♪Someday I won't be crying♪
Someday I won't be crying
♪I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♪
더 이상 상처주지 않기 위해 자신을 희생했다
CONSPIRACY
(음모)
Sister...
언니…
Kasane!
카사네
Do not undo the Red String.
빨간 줄 풀지 말아요
I want all available fighters here!
움직일 수 있는 사람 빨리 와서 도와줘
Nagi!
나기
Nagi, are you all right?
나기 괜찮아
Sister!
언니
Kasane...
카사네
Stop it!
그만해
If you don't...
그만하지 않으면…
Wait! Sister!
잠깐만요 언니
Sister!
언니
Don't go over there.
가지 마
Let go of me! Naomi...
손 놔요 나오미 나오미가…
What happened just now
아까… 어떻게 된 일인가요?
Naomi is...
나오미가…
This can't be happening...
어떻게
-Let me go! -Gemma.
-놔요 -겜마
I'm glad you're all right.
여러분 무사해서 참 다행이다
Major General Fubuki.
후부키 중대장님
Seto and Kyoka are safe.
세토와 쿄카도 무사해요
We eliminated all Others.
모든 괴이 다 치워버렸어
What matters now is...
지금 더 중요한 것은…
It was Naomi, am I right?
나오미 맞죠
Everyone, do not tell anyone what you witnessed today.
여러분 오늘 본 광경 나가서 소문내지 마세요
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻입니까
I meant what I said.
말 그대로다
This is for your safety.
이렇게 하는 것은 너희를 보호하기 위해서요
Our safety?
보호
What about Naomi?
근데…나오미는요
Naomi...
나오미…
I'll report Naomi's disappearance as killed in action.
나오미 전사 보고서를 제가 제출할 거예요
Killed in action?
전사라요
This isn't right.
어떻게 이럴 수가
Naomi is still alive.
나오미 죽지 않았어요
Understood.
알겠습니다
Gemma!
겜마
This is an order from the Major General.
중대장님의 명입니다.
Sorry, Gemma.
미안한다 겜마
Hold on, Kasane.
카사네 돌아와
Where are you going?
어디 갈건데
The mission is still ongoing. Do not wander off on your own.
아직 작전중이라서 함부로 움직이지 마세요
Kasane!
카사네
Fubuki. I should get going.
후부키 먼저 갈게
Very well.
그래
Nagi seems injured.
나기 다친 것 같아
Take him to a hospital.
병원에 데리고 가요
Gemma, I leave the rest to you.
겜마 부탁드린다
Understood.
네 알겠습니다
Tsugumi, look after Kasane.
츠구미 카사네 너한테 맡긴다
Naomi was strong and gentle.
나오미는 강하고 다정한 아이인데
Why...
그런데…
Loss is inevitable as long as we're a member of the OSF.
토벌군에 있으면 이런 이별이 피할 수 없다
We can only do our best to cope.
애써 넘어야 할까요…
Cursed Others.
그놈의 괴이
When you die, you can't slack off again.
죽으면 더이상 게으름 피울 수 없어
Kasane.
카사네
A member of OSF...
토벌군 멤버였더니
To make it worse, Yuito saw it.
심지어 유이토 그 사람들 때문에...
Leave them to me.
그들은 나에게 처리하도록 맡겨주세요
Not a word will get out.
조용히 처리하겠습니다
Very well. I'm counting on you.
그래 그럼 네가 가서 해라
Major General Spring.
스프링 소장
Thank you for your trust.
감사합니다
Sister...
언니…
NEW MESSAGE. DO YOU WISH TO PLAY IT?
(메시지 왔습니다 확인하겠습니까)
I was told Naomi died in the battle.
나오미 전사하는 소식 받았어
Why didn't you tell me?
왜 말 안 했어
Our dear Naomi...
우리 사랑하는 나오미…
We couldn't turn down the recruitment.
국가의 모집을 거절할 수 없어서
We left Naomi in your care.
어쩔 수 없이 나오미를 당신에게 맡겼는데
We were wrong about you.
우리가 사람을 잘 못 봤어
It was foolish to trust you.
우리가 멍청한 거야
From now on, do not contact us again.
앞으로도 우리랑 연락할 필요 없어
Are you going to report what happened to Naomi?
나오미에 관한 일을 보고하러 가는 길이에요
Seiran took Naomi.
나오미는 세이란가 데리고 갔어요
For Naomi to become human again,
나오미가 다시 인간으로 돌아가기 위해
we must rely on them.
그들에게 부탁할 수밖에 없어요
They will not kill Naomi right away.
그들은 나오미 죽이지 않을 거야
You have my word.
약속할게요
She can become human again?
인간으로 돌아가
You have no idea what happened.
무슨 일이 벌어졌는지 아무것도 모르는데
Yet you want me to trust you.
당신을 믿어달라고요
yet you doubt my words.
제가 한 말을 의심하고 있다
Even if you managed to get her back,
당신이 지금  나오미를 되찾아도
she will be terminated as an Other.
사람들이 나오미를 괴이로 생각하기 때문에 나오미 결국 목숨을 잃을 거예요
You must keep this incident a secret.
이번 일 절대 외부에 알려지면 안 돼요
Otherwise, not just Naomi,
안 그러면 나오미뿐만 아니라
even your life would be in danger.
당신의 존재까지 보장 드릴 수 없게 될 것이다
Are you going to kill me?
저를 죽일려고요
I don't think they would
그들은 아마...
actually kill you.
당신 "죽이지" 않을 거예요
Do not trust the people of New Himuka.
뉴히무카 저 사람들을 믿지마세요
Kasane? Are you all right?
카사네 괜찮아졌어요
You were there when it happened.
그때 당신도 그 자리에 있어서
I guess telling you shouldn't be considered treason.
알려줘도 소식 유출 아닌다
Seiran took Naomi?
나오미는 세이란가 데리고 갔어요
What is the OSF hiding from us?
토벌군이 아마 뭘 숨길려고 해요
Right.
맞다
Perhaps this has something to do with it.
이게 연관성 있는지 모르지만
Let me show you.
보여주고 싶어요
Wait! I kept it in here.
아니에요 안에 넣었어요
Ampoule?
앰풀
I found them by the abandoned tracks.
폐궤도에 떨어져 있는데
It could be some sort of drugs.
어떤 약 아닌까요
It has the mark of Seiran City on it.
위에 세이란시 표지도 있고
I've seen this before.
이거... 어디서 본 적 있는 것 같은데
At your home?
너희 집
Why would they have this?
왜 이런 거 있어요
It could be a clue.
이거 단서인질도 몰라
It'd be best if you didn't tell anyone.
되도록 다른 사람에게 알려지지 말아요
Very well.
알겠어요
As for Naomi...
나오미 그 일…
I'm sorry.
죄송해요
I knew that monster was Naomi.
그 괴이는 바로 나오미란 걸 알고 있어요
-But I... -Enough!
-근데… -그만하세요
I'll bring her back.
나오미를 되찾을 거예요
Just don't get in my way.
당신만 방해 안 한다면
I know this might be fancy words to you,
제가 그냥 빈말하고 있을지도 모르지만
but I want to help too.
최대한 도와줄게요
Those are fancy words indeed.
확실히 빈알이다
But I appreciate it./
그래도... 고마워요
How is Nagi?
맞다 나기는 괜찮아요
I lost contact with him after they rushed him to a hospital.
병원에 데려간 후 연락이 안 됐어요
He was a volunteer just like me.
나기가 저처럼 자원입대고
We went to the same training school.
같은 훈련 학교에 다녀요
But because of my family, people treated me like I was special.
제가 황실 사람이라서 어디가든 특별한 존재로 여겨지죠
Only Nagi treated me like a normal person.
나기만 평범하게 나랑 진했어요
Well, that wasn't very normal after all.
아니다 사실도 평범하지 않은데
I'd say he was overly friendly.
과하게 친했다고 말해야 할까
But I couldn't have come this far without him.
하지만 나기가 있어서 지금 저를 있게 되었어요
Nice to meet you, Kasane.
잘 부탁드립니다 카사네
Kasane.
카사네
Captain Seto.
세토 대장님
How are you holding up?
지금 다 괜찮아졌어요
I'm fine.
네
Are you sure? Don't push yourself too hard.
정말 무리하지 마요
I'll be fine. Thank you for your concern.
괜찮습니다 걱정하게 해서 죄송합니다
I'm not concerned about you.
걱정하는 거 아니고요
When you push yourself too hard in a battle,
전쟁터에서 누군가가 너무 무리하면
you put your comrades in danger.
동료가 곤경에 빠질 수 있다
You're not fighting alone.
당신은 혼자가 아니야
Don't forget, you still have those in the Kyoka Platoon.
쿄카 팀 멤버들도 같이 있는 거 잊지 말아요
Yes.
알겠습니다
I'm glad you understand.
알았으면 돼요
I should get going.
먼저 갈게
Are you sure about this?
정말 괜찮죠
Don't worry.
네 믿어주세요
This is a blind spot for the surveillance system.
여기는 감시 시스템의 사각지대다
The preparation is almost complete.
우리 준비 다 끝나고 있어요
What about our plan to take down OSF?
토벌군 와해 어떻게 되고 있어요
Proceed as usual.
계획대로 진행하고 있어요
This country will be ours...
이 나라를 우리가…
What? How is this happening?
뭐 어떻게 된거야
An alarm of unprecedented scale has been announced.
괴이성은 이전에 없었던 대량의 괴이 경보를 발포하였다
The location is centered around a ten-kilometer radius
위치는 쿠나도 고속도로를 중심으로
of the Kunad Highway.
반경 10킬로미터 이내이고
All soldiers of the OSF will be deployed.
괴이토벌군 전군이 출동하여 괴이를 토벌한다
We've issued an evacuation order to citizens of the Suoh capital.
이미 스오 시민에게 피난 지시를 내렸습니다
-Hurry up! -Get to the shelter.
-빨리 움직이세요 -빨리 피난 가세요
-They are overreacting. -The monsters are in Kunad, not here.
-크게 놀라지 마 -괴이 여기도 아니고 쿠나도에 나다잖아
Get to the shelter!
빨리 피난 가세요
All members, deploy!
전군 출동
Hinokami Platoon, move out.
수상팀 전진
Sakaki Platoon, move out.
선팀 전진
Kyoka, see you there.
쿄카 현장에서 봐요
Yes. Watch your back.
그래 조심해요
Where is Gemma going?
겜마 어디가요
The Others came in large numbers.
이번 괴이 수량이 많아서
He was assigned to command a special platoon.
그는 특별 편성한 기동대를 지휘하러 파견되었어요
That must be a lot of work.
정말 고생했다
Kageru.
카게로
It's nothing. I'm simply excited.
괜찮아 난 그저 너무 들떠 하고 있어
Kasane, are you all right?
카사네 괜찮아요
I'll be fine. I'll follow Captain Seto's order and not overdo myself.
괜찮아요 세토 대장에게 솔직히 말할게요 무리하지 않게
I can't die before I get Naomi back.
나오미 되찾기 전에 죽지 않을 거야
Great.
그래요 그럼
Captain Seto, everyone!
세토 대장님 여러분
Nagi?
나기
You're discharged, great.
잘됐어 퇴원했어요
How is your injury?
이제 괜찮아요
Why would you say that, Tsugumi?
츠구미 뭐 이런 말을 해요
Are you worried about me?
그렇게 걱정했어요
Oh my!
곤란하네
Captain Seto.
세토 대장님
Private Nagi Karman
나기 카르만상병
reporting to duty.
귀대하여 임무를 수행하겠습니다
We're glad you're back. Everyone was waiting for you.
돌아오면 돼 모두가 당신을 기다리고 있어요
Going back into action right after his discharge.
퇴원하자마자 전쟁터에 나가는구나
The army can be really harsh sometimes.
괴이토벌군은 정말 사람을 잘 부리네
I need to stretch my limbs anyway. I'll take this as my rehab therapy.
계속 안 움직면 몸에 녹이 슬 것이다 마침 재활으로 삼아 딱 좋아
Nagi...
나기…
Welcome back.
돌아와서 환영한다
But let's save the chitchat for later.
하지만 잔소리를 그만 하고
-Let's go. -Yes.
-갑시다 -네
Nagi, are you sure you'd be fine?
나기 이제 진짜 괜찬아요
My injury is almost healed.
거의 다 나았어요
See?
봐봐
No, I meant what happened to Naomi...
아니 나오미 말이야…
I'm still not over Naomi's death.
나오미 전사해서 충격 많이 받긴 하는데
But I can't keep sulking.
그렇다고 계속 의기소침할 수는 없잖아
Naomi's death?
전사
Naomi is still alive.
나오미 아직 살아 있는데
I know it's weird that she was turned into an Other...
괴이 되어 살고 있지만 좀 이상하긴 해…
What do you mean?
무슨 소리야
What do you mean she turned into an Other?
괴이 되어 무슨 뜻이죠
You shouldn't joke about something so serious.
이런 장남을 함부로 치지 않는 게 좋을 것 같아요
What if Kasane heard it?
카사네 들으면 어떡하죠
We will continue to fight the Others for the sake of New Himuka.
뉴히무카를 위해 괴이랑 싸울 거야
It will be tough, but we must keep moving forward.
힘들지만 계속 가야 해
All right, let's go.
자 갑시다
Nagi, what happened to you?
나기 너 도대체 왜 그래
Captain Seto.
세토 대장님
We should head to the forecast locations now.
예보에서 말한 위치에 거의 도착한 거 아니에요
We've met a few of them before...
도착하기 전에 괴이 몇 마리 만았는데
but not in this number.
이 정도 밖에 아닌 것 같은데
We could get off work early if there weren't many of them.
이것밖에 없다면 일찍 돌아갈 수도 있을 것이다
Indeed, it's too quiet here.
그러니까 여기 너무 조용한다
Wataru.
와타루
How is the surrounding area?
주변 상황은 어떤가요
This is different from the forecast.
확실히 괴이 예보와 다르다
Could there be an error?
뭐가 잘못됐나
I'll confirm the Other attacks...
지금 당장 괴이 확인해서…
Wataru? What's wrong, Wataru?
와타루 무슨 일 있어요
Haruka?
하루카…
Captain Seto, please respond.
세토 대장님 대답하세요
Captain?
대장님
Brother.
오빠
I can't get a hold of Captain Kyoka either.
저도 쿄카 대장랑 연결이 안 돼요
What? Could it be...
뭐 설마…
It's a jamming signal.
통신이 교란되었나
Tsugumi?
츠구미
Captain, we've been surrounded!
대장님 우리가 포위되었다
Those are OSF soldiers.
저기는…괴이토벌군
Were there other platoons
우리 말고
that were sent to this location?
다른 소대를 여기에 파견했나요
Gemma?
겜마
Gemma, what is this about?
겜마 뭐 할려고요
We could go home early today.
모처럼 일찍 들어갈 수 있는데
Don't you dare give us more work.
괸히 일을 늘리지 말아
Gemma, what is going on?
겜마 이게 어떻게 된 거야
Sorry, Kyoka.
쿄카 죄송해요
Seto, I can't believe you've done such a horrible experiment.
세토 이렇게 무서운 연구를 할 줄은 몰랐어요
What do you mean?
지금 무슨 말을 하고 있어요
You can stop pretending now.
모른 척 할 겁니까
What are you talking about? What do you want?
도대체 무슨 말을 하고 또 뭘 하고 있는 거죠
I'm confused.
이게 무슨 상화이야
All of you, stand back.
너희들은 빨리 물러나는 게 좋겠다
Luka...
루카
Luka Travers!
루카 트래버스
Do you think you can handle two Septentrions at once?
셉텐트리온 두 명을 이길 수 있다고 생각해요
Luka, what is going on here?
루카 이게 무슨 상화이야
I'll explain later.
나중에 설명할게요
Let me take care of these soldiers.
이 괴이토벌군들 제가 격퇴할게요
-Run while you... -If I'm your opponent,
-너희들 틈타 도망쳐… -제가 상대해줄게
will you still be as confident?
아직도 같은 말 나울 수 있어
Major General!
중대장님
Brother!
형
Luka, you've come at last.
루카 넌 역시 왔구나
Everyone, I'll handle him.
여러분 형은 제가 맡길게요
Ignorance!
유치한다
Brain field!
머리속 공간
Sclerokinesis, electrokinesis, and aerokinesis...
경질화 방전 그리고 공기 조작
Don't you remember?
잊었나
He can copy people's powers and use them as his own!
중대장가 남의 뇌능력을 복사해서 자신의 공격으로 될 수 있어
A brain eater.
브레인... 이터...
Major General Karen.
카렌 중대장님
Are you the mastermind behind this?
모든 걸 다 대장님이 계산한 겁니까
This country...
이 나라…
New Himuka has lied to you!
뉴히무카 우리를 속였어
Gemma.
겜마
My sister...
우리 언니…
You know what happened to Naomi!
나오미한테 무슨 일 생기는지 알아요
-Naomi? -What do you mean?
-나오미 -지금 이게 무슨 뜻이죠
I knew it.
역시…
The New Himuka Government is involved.
뉴히무카…그리고 정부랑 관련 있어…
Kasane!
카사네
Kasane, what do you mean?
카사네 이게 무슨 소리야
Answer me...
대답해요
Answer me, Gemma!
겜마 대답해
♪I don't need to let fate dictate me♪
운명의 지시 따라갈 필요 없다
♪Because I believe that I can rewrite it♪
꼭 바꿀 수 있다고 믿는다
♪I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♪
우리 앞으로도 계속 꿈을 꾸자
♪Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♪
아침 해가 휘황찬란하게 빛나다가 지고 있고
♪What's waiting for us at the world's end♪
세상 끝에 뭐가 기다렸는지
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going♪
미래의 등불은 영원히 꺼지지 않는다
♪Who can shake us♪
누가 우리를 위협하고 있는가
♪Who can define us♪
누가 우리에 대해 결정을 내릴 것인가
♪It's nothing less than our story♪
이것은 우리만의 이야기다
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♪
앞으로도 네 마음속 불빛이 영원히 꺼지지 않을 거야
RED STRINGS
(빨간 줄)